BYEONGJOO AHN

Porter Hall B5, 5000 Forbes Ave, Pittsburgh, PA 15213

Homepage: https://byeongjooahn.com & Email: bahn@cmu.edu

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interests are in computational imaging and computer vision. I am interested in identifying visible hints offered by our physical surroundings such as interreflections, and developing imaging systems extending the visibility far beyond human ability such as the reconstruction of objects that are not in the direct line of sight or those with strong self-occlusions.

EDUCATION

Carnegie Mellon University

Pittsburgh, PA Ph.D. Candidate in Electrical and Computer Engineering Sep. 2017 – Present

Advisors: Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan and Ioannis Gkioulekas

Seoul National University Seoul, Korea

Mar. 2012 - Feb. 2014 M.S. in Electrical Engineering and Computer Science

Advisor: Kyoung Mu Lee

Thesis: "Occlusion-Aware Motion Deblurring for Bilayer Scenes"

Outstanding Thesis Award

Seoul National University Seoul, Korea

B.S. in Electrical and Computer Engineering Mar. 2008 - Feb. 2012

Summa Cum Laude

WORK EXPERIENCE

Carnegie Mellon University

Research Assistant

Pittsburgh, PA Sep. 2017 – Present

· Developed a full-surround 3D imaging system of kaleidoscopic structured light, comprising a projector, a camera, and a kaleidoscope

· Developed an imaging method to reconstruct hidden 3D shapes from multiply scattered photon using time-of-flight (ToF) information at picosecond timescale resolution (a.k.a. Non-Line-of-Sight Imaging)

Snap Inc. (Remote) New York, NY

Research Intern with Shree Nayar and Jian Wang, Computational Imaging Group

May. 2020 - Aug. 2020

· Worked on improving Snapcode/QR code detection by increasing the maximum scanning distance

Korea Institute of Science and Technology

Seoul, Korea

Research Scientist (Military Service), Center for Imaging Media Research

Mar. 2014 - Aug. 2017

- · Developed multiple-camera capture system with 3D multi-view deblurring algorithm for dynamic 3D facial reconstruction
- · Developed polarized lighting system with an algorithm for real time acquisition of specular and diffuse normal maps from minimal number of polarized images
- · Developed web application for Korean food classification using Caffe and Flask web server

HP Labs Palo Alto, CA Jan. 2012 - Feb. 2012

Research Intern with Irwin Sobel

· Developed 3D video mobile controller using PTZ robot and Android phone

PUBLICATIONS

"Kaleidoscopic Structured Light"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Ioannis Gkioulekas, Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan *ACM Transactions on Graphics (Proc. SIGGRAPH ASIA)*, 2021

"Convolutional Approximations to the General Non-Line-of-Sight Imaging Operator"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Akshat Dave, Ashok Veeraraghavan, Ioannis Gkioulekas, Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan *IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV)*, 2019 (Oral Presentation)

"Occlusion-Aware Video Deblurring with a New Layered Blur Model"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Tae Hyun Kim, Wonsik Kim, Kyoung Mu Lee *arXiv preprint arXiv:1611.09572*, 2016

"Reduced Illumination Patterns for Acquisition of Specular and Diffuse Normal Maps"

 ${\bf Byeongjoo\ Ahn},$ Junghyun Cho, Taekyung Yoo, Ig-Jae Kim

ACM SIGGRAPH ASIA Poster, 2016

"Dynamic Scene Deblurring"

Tae Hyun Kim, Byeongjoo Ahn, Kyoung Mu Lee

IEEE International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2013

| AWARDS AND HONORS | |
|--|-----------|
| Doctoral Study Abroad Scholarship, Korea Foundation for Advanced Studies | 2017 |
| Fulbright Graduate Study Award (gratefully declined), Fulbright | 2017 |
| Best Poster Award, KIST R&D EXPO | 2014 |
| Outstanding Thesis Award, Department of EECS, Seoul National University | 2014 |
| Honorable Mention Award, Samsung Humantech Paper Award | 2014 |
| Graduate Scholarship, Kwanjeong Educational Foundation | 2012 |
| Presidential Science Scholarship, Korea Student Aid Foundation | 2008 |
| INVITED TALKS | |
| "Kaleidoscopic Imaging for Full-Surround 3D Reconstruction" | |
| · Topics in 3D Vision Workshop, Seoul National University | Jan. 2022 |
| · TechTalk, Meta Reality Labs Research, Pittsburgh | Apr. 2022 |

TEACHING

Teaching Assistant, Carnegie Mellon University

- · 15-463/663/862 Computational Photography
- · Recitation for 18-290 Signals and Systems

Fall 2020

Spring 2019, 2020

SERVICES

Reviewer, CVPR 2019-2022; ICCV 2019-2021; ECCV 2020-2022; BMVC 2019; ICLR 2022; NeurIPS 2022

Student Volunteer, ACCV 2012; ICCP 2021

Volunteer, Camera Building Workshop as part of Gelfand Outreach Program at CMU (2019)

Mentor, CMU AI Mentoring Program (2021)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Proficient with MATLAB, Python, C/C++; Conversant with C#, JavaScript

GRADUATE COURSEWORK

| 16-889 | Learning for 3D Vision | Spring 2022 |
|---------|----------------------------------|-------------|
| 15-868 | Physics-based Rendering | Spring 2021 |
| 33-353 | Intermediate Optics | Fall 2020 |
| 15-858 | Discrete Differential Geometry | Spring 2020 |
| 18-771 | Linear Systems | Fall 2019 |
| 10-707 | Deep Learning | Spring 2019 |
| 10-725 | Convex Optimization | Fall 2018 |
| 16-823 | Physics based Methods in Vision | Spring 2018 |
| 10-701 | Introduction to Machine Learning | Spring 2018 |
| 16-720B | Computer Vision | Fall 2017 |
| 18-793 | Image and Video Processing | Fall 2017 |
| 36-705 | Intermediate Statistics | Fall 2017 |
| | | |

Last updated: Apr 11, 2021